This flight goes nonstop to hell.
Fight or Flight is a action, comedy, thriller film directed by James Madigan.
A mercenary takes on the job of tracking down a target on a plane but must protect that
target when they're surrounded by people trying to kill both of them.
Lucas Reyes, played by Josh Hartnett.
Isha, played by Charithra Chandran.
Katherine Brunt, played by Katee Sackhoff.
Cayenne, played by Marko Zaror.
Master Lian, played by JuJu Chan.
Aaron Hunter, played by Julian Kostov.
Fight or Flight is a 2025 action comedy film directed by James Madigan in
his feature film debut, and written by Brooks McLaren and D.
It stars Josh Hartnett as a man who is recruited to identify and protect a wanted criminal aboard a
commercial airline; Charithra Chandran, Marko Zaror, and Katee Sackhoff also star.
Fight or Flight was released in the United Kingdom on February
28, 2025, and in the United States on May 9.
The film received positive reviews from critics,
who praised Hartnett's performance.
The film explores themes of mercenary, dark comedy, frantic, fight or flight.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and intense.